[
    {
        "question": "Russia",
        "answer": "Moscow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sweden",
        "answer": "Stockholm"
    },
    {
        "question": "Estonia",
        "answer": "Tallinn"
    },
    {
        "question": "Latvia",
        "answer": "Riga"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finland",
        "answer": "Helsinki"
    },
    {
        "question": "Luxemburg",
        "answer": "Luxemburg"
    },
    {
        "question": "Italy",
        "answer": "Roma"
    },
    {
        "question": "Australia",
        "answer": "Canberra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fiji",
        "answer": "Suva"
    },
    {
        "question": "Peru",
        "answer": "Lima"
    }
]
